I still see your shadows in my room
Can't take back the love that I gave you
It's to the point where I love and I hate you
And I cannot change you, so I must replace you, oh
Easier said than done, I thought you were the one
Listenin' to my heart instead of my head
You found another one, but I am the better one
I won't let you forget me
I'll do it over again
I didn't want it to end
I watch it blow in the wind
I should've listened to my friends
Leave this shit in the past, but I want it to last
You were made outta plastic, fake
I was tangled up in your drastic ways
Who knew evil girls had the prettiest face?
You gave me a heart that was full of mistakes
I gave you my heart and you made heartbreak
I have these lucid dreams where I can't move a thing
Thinking of you in my bed
You were my everything
Thoughts of a wedding ring
Now I'm just better off dead
Now I'm just better off dead (Uh)
Now I'm just better off dead (Uh, uh)
Now I'm just better off dead (Uh, uh, uh)
I still see your shadows in my room
Can't take back the love that I gave you
It's to the point where I love and I hate you
And I cannot change you, so I must replace you, oh
Easier said than done, I thought you were the one
Listenin' to my heart instead of my head
You found another one, but I am the better one
I won't let you forget me
Leave this shit in the past, but I want it to last
You were made outta plastic, fake
I was tangled up in your drastic ways
Who knew evil girls had the prettiest face?